http://www.msuu.org/privacy-policy

Jump to navigation
Privacy Policy
This web site is owned and operated by the Michael Servetus Unitarian Society (MSUS). We recognize that visitors to our site may be concerned about the information they provide to us, and how we treat that information. This Privacy Policy addresses those concerns. This policy may be changed or updated from time to time. If you have any questions please email us.
The first principle of the member societies of the Unitarian Universalist Association (UUA) is that we will covenant to affirm and promote the inherent worth and dignity of every person. We believe that this principle impels MSUS to protect the privacy of visitors to our website.
Personal Information
We only collect personal information from our visitors on a voluntary basis. Personal information may include name, address, phone number, email address. We do not require this information to obtain access to any part of the public portion of our site.
The personal information we collect is only used by us to process a request that has been placed by a visitor. Typically this is in the form of voluntary submittals of similar information for survey purposes or for event registrations.
We do not give, sell or rent this personal information to other organizations.
We Care About Doing It Right
In addition to maintaining privacy and security controls over information you share with us, MSUS works to accurately process your information. However, if inaccuracies occur, we will make every effort to correct them in a timely manner. To report any web site inaccuracies or for questions about MSUS's Internet Privacy Policy please email us.
This Week's Services
The Art of Stillness
Use the MSUS Zoom room to attend this service.
Pico Iyer, author of the “The Art of Stillness: Adventures...
12/13/2020 - 10:30am
Read More
Upcoming Events
Dec11
Calendar of Stillness:
Crafting Day04:00pm to 05:00pm
Dec12
Story Telling06:30pm to 07:30pm
Dec12
Cancelled:
Small Group Spiritual Direction Offered by Rev Laura05:15pm to 06:45pm
Dec16
Music Zoom - Choir07:00pm to 09:00pm
Dec17
Virtual Meeting:
Third Thursday for those 60+11:00am to 12:00pm
Dec18
Calendar of Stillness:
LearningReligious Education (RE)
Who Was Michael Servetus?
© 2020. All rights reserved.
Terms & Conditions  |  Privacy Policy
